var data = {
    "name":"id_rsa",
    "seed":"h7OuydLdqE8wIBwrvfBVPGOSFQ0iwcCAOEVHek5oXWDTNEMQEULAVMUXHgTJDUzhs2vyjpXhCSJZToOWKKRHBCWEtoAdm7quOLnm5uyyrJfCm7aNVWtDFuFyheU1RHM7YZhcyClpezLKvRVOxU5UwKWmRnrYtrfa9s2poMEshknzWhY@K28JZwVOqYvkMyBZc4u{TQqbW31GDzY0JDCU1Iqr1w8635pWIg4A6n0m9c34VkIBinFqkoElYGloCaaNpImv1ggBCY8=epJyupgx6pl0Id*bm28klG96j0OtuJKKkvBs5DwKitB4KYiTNkEkiUjfOA0vrAfv7vAddkoOTdHhP31Zq5gk6E5beyMJxs3N'b3d5qiFz/SpLcRPYlEkj6pnIq2MS1rRvV7uGNulIeyr4sfd\"GRBfhZ7DZ'VENOPvcGKY3zZqtkzBe68gYWAOEsmd8ypuzQmNEMPEEIN0atRiexnH8FgmlZz+MWj3K0Fe6eN0UrnLxJxiXpifZnAcULG5uKEOnWSOZmjZF57B6Tm]bU5W62izofahga#2f8Aw3DQpkv7CBI;1kPky`5YweZQiDY2HZCgR6psuIMvA1Vngi6FQXD03sWT2H0D01vVyG{~AVKzzt8j4IJdiKDuWhdhWl5F7IEn^}3gjPoTs1UBDecGULirOwOSl6XL0y4r9A0Sk>ClJYoqBAlRvcJJbafD0djeY6o1iO6UG}0kUcshLNEzqsaOQGtIic1:B2>ZpMX92gvrPaO2wF58h6Go9goISpKPzaVeA94RKK/iUw98LzO1sZTPV2hcHzkvKARHBwWESSZPJKH>I597bRd8<gQDvjEOx740JliFLpbR1F729XK1AdMlBj8Smg3JX`3uTVUQKPaG302hGK40YX4H6RX\\2TYehiaLvzVbw1EvXe12YskY5he$2sTYdzERo\"SIuQgswADbqgjqbVCoElAaJ3qzDQtv7KKngMzqtXMB3'i9PGsTRd2|w\"z4kLK4lBhn*wrjFsvk9OnHKFiUYii5EPoi\"wEasV1se4b77kIqGaOWbtwGpMWf4dvPQiaoqLXoyGRR8CElpGqHeHBvw7yZ532GG4k4bkDnj01OAAXzVH45fa6B7YM7xC3ECP6m\\kcYhDQkD8NRq7pljIBVDX6rqCO~yODbh57yPGOSaPXDOAMXYiKn8fGcixpENjek,Hv7BQfFfGG75aOt1WAdBGSVGTr3DJjv3ARdWnNiiK5VnPllGrN4yfwg#DkXBlTFKzrkIlZ80UJf1iArSIGlakGtoLu#kyQ8xp/IxoFXE|2d$WcCrU0RP7Lgtj7vF3JvgOQbkgRu9Mwf4aDyo3R8JAIMuAEzLglwfRa70fTJGGd1LtFixpz]VFO8Ielt3MM>YO5nuON5rTiMwKy63sSbkCNpXzpPydY2J8WJe8wGCuGE28VJtsE0wOsg4707xq4bdqN.UoFuba4fXOfAK6Usb55A93LTVa\"E5LXV'LgGvMFWxs4oN4LV6WdW14S9RaIeYhSyIECGUCXR9khKRQYwJPqJULX'QKziehlIJ/u>D2mDgB<t02XxLxvle6d4U=q0zdM5vxhSla=zWZnHlGkOKDoflM0E1bIGOHCe9AfhuiQceXwUe6gA0dvwdV5FbXaY1sluyajsJRtIOEmw4sVfAF3eZojmDCGmMtLkksPC9/kcqV19f26hag2AOEVdeAZjtQsTSY7reOa8sQbjlq2WFYPEt60aAIFzak2hs6FpjAN|",
    "qas":[{"question":"無免許運転でつかまったのは?","answers":["愛媛","神奈川","鳥取","山梨","福井","埼玉","栃木","広島","香川","東京","鹿児島","石川","大阪","岩手","大分","高知","京都","沖縄","千葉","奈良","青森","長崎","北海道","静岡","福岡","福島","群馬","佐賀","滋賀","山形","茨城","山口","三重","新潟","宮崎","兵庫","島根","富山","熊本","長野","岡山","徳島","宮城","秋田","岐阜","愛知","和歌山"]},{"question":"友達の従姉妹が美人だったのは?","answers":["富山","福井","鳥取","和歌山","奈良","宮崎","佐賀","山口","島根","宮城","神奈川","京都","愛媛","岩手","福岡","兵庫","長崎","長野","徳島","茨城","石川","鹿児島","山梨","新潟","山形","秋田","香川","北海道","栃木","岐阜","大分","広島","青森","群馬","三重","静岡","愛知","埼玉","東京","千葉","沖縄","熊本","大阪","岡山","高知","福島","滋賀"]},{"question":"店のベランダを踏み抜いたのは?","answers":["京都","鹿児島","埼玉","岐阜","大分","滋賀","新潟","富山","三重","宮城","栃木","千葉","福井","奈良","徳島","佐賀","愛知","北海道","山梨","愛媛","山形","鳥取","福岡","福島","宮崎","大阪","兵庫","静岡","東京","石川","岡山","岩手","香川","高知","山口","島根","長野","群馬","熊本","秋田","広島","神奈川","沖縄","和歌山","長崎","茨城","青森"]},{"question":"針金作ってるのは?","answers":["青森","宮崎","栃木","奈良","北海道","静岡","香川","富山","広島","東京","大分","茨城","兵庫","千葉","鹿児島","宮城","滋賀","京都","佐賀","石川","福岡","秋田","島根","岩手","岡山","長崎","長野","和歌山","徳島","熊本","三重","群馬","大阪","鳥取","山梨","神奈川","山形","新潟","福井","愛媛","高知","埼玉","岐阜","山口","沖縄","福島","愛知"]},{"question":"夜の猿が怖いのは?","answers":["東京","広島","徳島","栃木","神奈川","京都","鳥取","和歌山","山梨","秋田","大分","鹿児島","滋賀","島根","宮崎","兵庫","岩手","大阪","茨城","愛知","佐賀","青森","石川","愛媛","岡山","山形","高知","静岡","奈良","群馬","北海道","埼玉","長野","新潟","千葉","富山","福岡","福井","岐阜","宮城","香川","長崎","熊本","山口","沖縄","三重","福島"]},{"question":"川で流されたのは?","answers":["徳島","山梨","埼玉","福岡","島根","栃木","佐賀","香川","長崎","広島","兵庫","新潟","東京","鹿児島","宮崎","千葉","和歌山","神奈川","長野","宮城","大阪","奈良","愛媛","秋田","岐阜","沖縄","山形","石川","鳥取","富山","京都","滋賀","岩手","高知","茨城","群馬","静岡","福島","熊本","愛知","福井","山口","三重","岡山","青森","大分","北海道"]},{"question":"宿の食事が絶望的だったのは?","answers":["福井","富山","高知","山形","奈良","兵庫","福岡","島根","鹿児島","千葉","秋田","山梨","大阪","愛知","長崎","静岡","徳島","香川","鳥取","宮崎","茨城","京都","北海道","佐賀","群馬","山口","沖縄","神奈川","東京","青森","岐阜","埼玉","愛媛","長野","石川","岩手","宮城","大分","広島","滋賀","三重","和歌山","熊本","岡山","新潟","福島","栃木"]},{"question":"段ボールを買うのは?","answers":["神奈川","愛媛","島根","佐賀","富山","長崎","兵庫","岩手","香川","和歌山","宮城","大阪","東京","山梨","北海道","栃木","奈良","福岡","石川","愛知","長野","千葉","静岡","徳島","岡山","群馬","秋田","茨城","高知","福井","青森","山形","滋賀","沖縄","宮崎","三重","山口","埼玉","熊本","福島","鳥取","鹿児島","岐阜","大分","京都","新潟","広島"]},{"question":"ギターを弾いて怒られたのは?","answers":["山口","愛知","香川","広島","神奈川","三重","静岡","東京","秋田","埼玉","福井","大阪","山梨","宮崎","徳島","宮城","滋賀","兵庫","北海道","鹿児島","千葉","青森","佐賀","沖縄","大分","岐阜","福岡","山形","和歌山","島根","熊本","京都","長野","栃木","奈良","岩手","愛媛","富山","鳥取","石川","茨城","新潟","福島","群馬","岡山","長崎","高知"]},{"question":"ビフテキをおかわりしたのは?","answers":["徳島","愛媛","福岡","岐阜","香川","長野","愛知","宮崎","三重","滋賀","佐賀","広島","福井","神奈川","栃木","熊本","鹿児島","青森","奈良","山梨","富山","和歌山","鳥取","埼玉","長崎","沖縄","石川","山口","新潟","岡山","宮城","茨城","山形","兵庫","秋田","島根","東京","北海道","京都","岩手","大阪","福島","群馬","千葉","大分","高知","静岡"]}]}

exports.data = data
